Thank you for watching!
Kettle and Idol
This will be the main project.
Now, please call the title!
My three main elements
Alright.
Now, this is the section where you will be introduced to the three elements that make up Hanane.
The idea is to let you know more about that idol.
Now, may I have you write down the three elements and bring them out?
Yes. Here are my three major elements.
May I ask you to read them?
Sister
2. performance at all costs
3. food
I see.
Enjoy the next installment!
What's this about?
Well, I am the younger sister among the members.
I see.
I'm a spoiled brat.
All the members are older sisters.
Yes.
I'm a bit spoiled.
What exactly do you mean by two spoiled brats?
I spill food on my clothes just by living.
You spill food on your clothes just by living?
Yes, sir.
That's new.
I always find something on my clothes.
You're spoiled.
And then I'm like...
"Oh, she's got something on her.
I noticed it.
And I always ask the members to wipe it off.
And someone is taking these videos.
There are a lot of videos like that.
Have you ever spilled something like this?
I've never spilled something like this before.
I don't think I've ever spilled anything like that before.
There's a cheese in the "Nuritoto".
Nuritoto...
There's something in it.
Yes, it's there.
You used to eat it normally?
Yes, I did.
And then...
I ate it all...
What?
There's cheese all over the place.
Oh, the costume?
So, you know, it's just the skin.
That's too bad.
Do you spill it on your costume?
Whenever I'm in costume.
Or put a hoodie on.
Or put something on here first.
I can't even eat my food.
Oh, so that's the rule.
Hey, Kanon.
You're going to spill it.
If you spill it on your outfit...
You tend to do that a lot.
That's right.
Well, well, well.
Oh, my God.
Heh.
What else do you have in common with your sister?
Well, I enjoy messing with the members.
Oh?
Um, yes.
Her name is Shieri.
She's the one who watches out for the members the most.
She's the one who looks out for the members the most.
Shieri-chan's eyes look like tadpoles.
her eyes look like tadpoles.
Her eyes are like this.
The tip of her eye is like a tadpole.
Her eyes are so cute.
They look like tadpoles.
That's why...
Totoro's
"Your house is like a tadpole
You know that line, right?
Do you have it?
That's right.
And I always say to Shieri-chan
Shieri's eyes
tadpole
I say "tadpole".
She says, "Your eyes are tadpoles.
Oh, they're cute.
They're cute.
Is this allowed?
I see.
She's definitely my sister.
I can't hate her, can I?
That's nice.
No, no, no. Thank you.
I can't hate you.
My catchphrase is.
My catchphrase is "Angel name Konamaike.
It's a catchphrase that idols often put in their catchphrases.
in their catchphrases.
Tenshi na Konamaike
By myself.
I call myself this name.
I can't hate it.
In Kyushu, there was an extraordinary
There was a Depression, wasn't there?
Thank you very much.
I love idols who give their best performance.
I love this show.
Mr. Daikichi
Mr. Mountstone. Mr. Muraguchi.
Mr. Sho
Mr. Toshihiko provided this program!
Thank you very much!